masssterchief
The time has come...
for our company to...
to start restructuring, right?
What? Does this mean that I can quit early?
Plus, the retirement benefits will be increased.
It's only for employees over 50, Riko.
So I can't take up this offer, right?
Do you want to retire early that badly?
For sure.
While the salary goes up, the performance goes down.
All the older employees who represents a negative legacy,
the company cuts them off by offering them retirement benefits that coincide with the time when they're still able to pursue their second career.
I think that it's a very rational move for the company.
Can you say all of that to our three crows?
It's not rational at all.
So you do understand what I'm saying.
I had an awakening the other day.
I wonder who will take up the offer to retire early?
Yamauchi of the Safety Management Department,
it seems like he's really into making soba with his wife.
Retire and then open up a restaurant, the best case scenario, right?
It's yellow light for him.
And my classmate Sudo, it seems like he's been watching youtube videos about investments lately.
That is a red light for him.
But we're going to cling to this company with both hands.
I won't let go, don't you agree, Kijimura-san?
You're right.
It hurts.
Good work.
I can't do it.
The parts are way too detailed.
Space Battleship Yamato 2202, the final battle.
Those tiny parts are just like the countless stars in space.
Building the Yamato is quite difficult.
I suddenly raised the difficulty way too high.
I give up.
If Shinji was able to do it, there's no way that you couldn't do it.
You got heated looking at Shinji-san's Eva, don't you?
Get fired up, Zakunee!
I don't want to.
All of this for the cannons?!
Those tiny parts are delicate.
The impact of cutting it with a nipper might break it.
Gently cut it off using that cutter.
I'm scared because I might break it again.
It's the trauma from building the Zaku, right?
Assembling it is only the start.
The real battle lies ahead!
My Yamato...
I wonder if it can fly to space or not.
It's going to fly using the wave engine!
Assembling it is only the start.
Komukai.
Yes?
What are you doing? Are you thinking about where to go for lunch?
I brought my own lunch today.
I see.
Can I ask you to come up with a new goods idea for Manten Nodoame-san?
Idea for new goods?
-Yes.
Inuzuka-kun, that is something that I do every year...
That's right.
Forgive me for not noticing it sooner.
What?
We should leave this kind of work to the young generation.
Well, that's...
As the Acting Chief, it's more than enough for you to just oversee things as an observer.
Don't you agree, Komukai?
Yes.
Observer...
Well, go say something to him.
Kijimura-san, I'm honored to be working with you.
Likewise.
There's Kijimura behind Manten.
Learn from him, okay?
Yes.
Like an observer, okay?
Riko and Kijimura-san teaming up is so unusual.
The oldest employee in the Events Department, Acting Chief Kijimura.
Even when Inuzuka-san, who was once his junior,
passed him and became his boss, he's still chill.
I also want to be someone as prideless as him.
You don't actually think so, right?
Good analysis!
Do you think that we should go the same route as last year's comfy cushion?
But, I think that a new project might be a good thing.
A new project?
Like bath salts from Manten Herb.
Is that a no?
The client loved last year's goods.
You don't have to change route.
I will take the same route as last years.
Please do.
I'm very sorry, I slept in the train and have arrived at
Tobu Zoological Park, which is on the exact opposite direction from our destination.
You even came to an amazing place.
I've been staying up late lately...
I'm terribly sorry.
It looks like that I won't make it in time for the presentation.
Understood.
I'm going to do the presentation instead.
I'm really sorry.
I'm praying for your success.
It's going to be okay, take care!
Cushy pillow?
Yes, it's a pillow that can make you feel the relaxing sensation of Manten Nodoame.
Isn't this basically the same thing as last year's cushy cushion?
The theme for this year is a good night sleep, so we went with a pillow.
Don't you have a brand new project instead?
A brand new project?
It's okay.
Eh? Are you sure?
The feedback that we got from the customers last year was great.
I think that we should go with this for this year's goods.
I agree.
Thank you very much.
Okay then, please excuse me.
Are you sure going with that project?
Kijimura-san has been working with this company longer than me, so we must tread carefully.
30 years was it?
I heard that some of our board members is indebted to him.
Is that how it is?
Old kit?
I'm terribly sorry, Kijimura-san.
Don't mention it, good work.
How was the presentation?
They accepted the project.
The cushy pillow?
As expected from "There's Kijimura behind Manten".
Don't mention it, I didn't do anything that was praiseworthy
Eh?
Can I talk to you about something, Kijimura-san?
About what?
About the product exhibition at Kirari Mall,
there are talks that Shinji and I will be taking over this year's event.
What? Why all of a sudden?
It's a work that requires strength, doesn't it?
I feel bad to leave this work to you every year.
I don't think that is true though.
We young people should be the ones who put our bodies to work!
I see.
I leave it to you then.
Okay, I'll whip Shinji into shape!
Isn't that great, Shinji?
Please switch places with me, Nakano-san.
Do your best.
Hey.
President.
Don't call me that, we're classmates after all.
I mean, the president is the president.
I heard that you're still in charge of Manten-san?
Yes.
That sure bring back memories.
It's been 30 years, huh?
Please let FUNFUN CREATE be in charge of the event.
Okay, let's work together.
Thank you very much.
They were the first client that we secured, right?
It's been 30 years since that day.
I'm the only one who didn't change at all.
Being in charge of one client for that long is an amazing thing.
People around me is being considerate because I'm old.
Don't say such a thing.
It's sad without you in the company.
Sad...
That's all?
As the acting chief, it's more than enough for you to just oversee things as an observer.
Kijimura-san has been working with this company longer than me, so we must tread carefully.
We young people should be the ones who put our bodies to work!
[Early Retirement Application Form]
I guess it's time to move on...
Good work.
Are you going to the usual place again?
That's right, but I'm exhausted because it's super difficult delivery.
Since when have you become a plastic model mom?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Komukai-san, could it be that you are currently building the Yamato?
What?
I didn't know that there's a model shop close to the company.
I found this place by chance.
Good evening.
Zakunee.
Who did you bring along today?
Welcome.
I'm Komukai-san's colleague, Kijimura.
He wanted to come after I told him about this place.
Same generation as me?
Very nice.
Old men are welcomed here.
Thank you very much.
This is so nostalgic.
I was a modeller back in the day.
What? I couldn't tell at all.
It was a long time ago.
I was so into it for a time, that my wife gave me an earful.
That happens quite a lot to a modeller.
Did you build Gunplas?
No, I mainly built ships or boats.
A scale model specialist, huh?
Very nice.
Yassan is in the mood.
This is it.
Yamato.
These are quite the tiny parts.
Even though I'm clumsy, I managed to get this far.
No no, you did great.
It's all thank to my support.
It's better if you didn't say that out loud.
I don't know how to finish it.
Do you have an idea of how you want to paint it?
Because it's Yamato, I wanted it to look strong, cool...
I see.
That's all.
You can't imagine what comes after that?
That's right.
You've hit the imagination wall.
Imagination wall?
You have a vague idea of what you want to do, but you don't have the details drawer to pull it out from.
A drawer...
He said something good.
Are you familiar with Space Battleship Yamato in the first place?
I can sing the chorus of it.
In the year of 2199, humanity is one year away from extinction due to radiation contamination that was caused by an alien invasion.
Humanity used the wave engine that was brought by the Queen of the Iscandar and installed it to the battleship Yamato that was sunk during the Pacific war.
Space Battleship Yamato tells the story of the journey to the planet Iscandar to retrieve a device that can cleanse the Earth of its radiation damage.
He said the same thing as Yassan.
It is important to imagine what battles Yamato went through as it traveled through the vastness of space,
and to express that using paint!
It's not the usual Kijimura-san.
The real deal has come to this place.
Excuse me.
If you're willing,
do you mind helping me out?
What?
Are you sure?
Yes.
I want to get over the imagination wall together.
Understood.
If that's the case, then I would like to everything starting from the basecoat.
But, I can't finish the whole thing in just one day.
What?
That's a veteran for you.
Isn't this basically the same thing as last year's cushy cushion?
Don't you have a brand new project instead?
But, I think that a new project might be a good thing.
No.
Let's try something new.
Something new?
I see what he's doing.
What is that you're using?
Smooth clear spray.
It removes the gloss characteristic of plastic models and creates a rough surface.
This way, we don't have to paint everything and make use of it's original color.
So we can enjoy the colors of the original materials?
That's right.
He sure knows his stuff.
It's common knowledge for a modeller.
You're so hard on him.
Next, is the filter liquid.
You're using that much?!
Then by wiping the painted parts like this, it gives the plastic model a refined look.
A refined look?
It means making it look good.
Let's do it then.
Okay.
Next up is rust.
Would you like to do the honors, Komukai-san?
How do you paint rust again?
Well...
Rust actually erodes gradually from these metal-to-metal joints.
So you have to paint it while imagining the natural phenomenon that occurs in real life.
I think that I can picture it somehow.
That is what is called the imagination wall.
There's nothing that you can do today, Yassan.
Picture the things that the Yamato has been through.
Kijimura-san.
That is also how the pros do things.
I love doing things like this.
I entered this line of work with the intention of doing scenography for theme parks and such.
I see.
I only want to enjoy going to theme parks.
But,
there was only 5 of us working for the company back in the day
and so I was so busy getting the jobs that were in front of us.
At that time, the first client that I and the current President managed to secure
was Manten Nodoame-san.
The President and you are classmates?
I was a daredevil back in the day.
A daredevil? You?
Is it surprising?
I can't imagine it at all
You always honest, don't you?
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
It's great hearing that from you.
Lastly, let's peel off the masking tape.
I'm shaking.
It's going to be alright.
I want to sneeze.
Hold it in.
It's done.
Space Battleship Yamato.
Give birth!
Wow.
I can see what the Yamato has been through.
Good work.
The dirty Kijimura has appeared!
You have a knack for this, Komukai-san
I want to pass the imagination wall again.
Painting is not just about coloring.
Imagine just what kind of adventures that this 1/1000 scale of Yamato has actually been through,
the goal is to get close to what we have in mind as possible.
It is truly the ultimate imagination!
What's wrong?
I'm shocked.
Shocked?
I see that you also get fired up.
I'm Kijimura the Buddha now, right?
I've remembered the good old days.
I want to build another plastic model with you again.
If the opportunity arises.
What? Kijimura-san?
I want him to be the leader for this project.
It's not a project that an Acting Chief should do.
I want to work with him again.
By the way, why are you being so considerate towards Kijimura-san?
Well, he's the oldest person here and it's not like I'm being considerate or anything.
What's the harm then?
If he wants to do it then it's okay.
By the way, it's rare seeing you this assertive.
You're right.
It's rare.
It's not a bad thing.
Me?
It's a floral event in Tokyo, I'd like to ask you to supervise the entire decoration.
Why are you coming to me once again?
The Yamato was amazing.
That's only a plastic model.
"The spirit of craftsmanship works on anything."
Yassan said so.
But, doing this work after all this time...
Is it because you're an Acting Chief?
The Acting Chief is only my title.
Okay, let's do it.
Thank you very much.
We're back.
Good work.
A new plastic model.
Did you build that yourself?
There's no way.
I got Kijimura-san to help me build it.
This is amazing.
I see that you also build plastic models, Kijimura-san.
It was my hobby back in the day.
Oh yeah!
I'm currently making a character figurine for our client with Nakano-san,
but we can't get the color of the sample just right.
Can you take a look?
Let me see that.
-Here you go
This is due to the undercoating.
Undercoating?
I see.
The process of undercoating is to ensure that the topcoat adheres properly to the surface of the material.
This sample seems to have skipped that step.
If it's okay with you, will you come with us to the factory to check it?
Me?
Yes.
I don't mind.
Thank you very much.
The young ones loves Kijimura-san.
You and Kijimura-san have different social skills after all.
What do you mean by that?
That was rude of me.
Rude? Does that mean that you meant it?
Not at all.
I see
What do you mean by that?
Kijimura-san...
Let's see...
Please take a look at this color sample.
Okay.
After you spray the sub,
I mean the undercoat.
After that you...