masssterchief
Good morning...
Was that Komukai-san?
That's right.
Good morning.
Thank you so much, Komukai speaking.
Yes.
Yes, thank you very much.
About that, please let me check it one more time.
Shinji.
Yes.
-Give this to Department 1.
What?
Don't say that.
I'm going to take some water, so I'll take it.
Is that so?
Let's have lunch together.
Sure. Do you mind that we have a yellow-colored dish?
Yellow? Why is that?
It's my lucky color today.
Oyakodon.
Okay.
Mass production-type...
Come again?
The way that you're starting your love is a mass-production type.
Are you in a one-sided relationship, Riko-san?
Who is that person? From back home?
In the company? From an app?
In the company, huh...
Is he in Department 3? Department 2? Or Department 1?
Department 1, huh...
Oishi-san?
Asai-san?
Oishi-san.
Oishi-san huh? I see that you're going for him.
I didn't say a word.
What's wrong with it?
They just said "Love", didn't they?
That's right.
Office romance
Could it be an affair?
Of course not.
Office romance is hard after all.
I wonder who the person is.
Okay then, I'm going to teach her the basics...
No, I'm going to teach her all about love.
That's sexual harassment.
That's power harassment.
Your clothes, hair, nails, your a bit expensive hand cream, fixing your make-up, lucky color,
and hanging around when you go pass Department 1.
It's confirmed then.
Your feelings for him developed because of the Mini 4WD, right?
I'm not saying a word.
We can't help you out if you don't admit to it.
What?
Please let us help you.
I did this after looking up various things.
It's cute.
I agree.
Men does not look at our nails, huh.
I'm going to improve.
Does Oishi-san like this kind of thing?
There's no data regarding that.
There must be something.
He's workaholic?
He loves Mini 4WD and Sambomaster
What kind of girls does he like?
By the way, he's single, right?
First things first, we must learn about our enemy,
During competition too, the key of success is to know the client.
We have to learn everything about him.
[Big Stone Investigation HQ]
I heard Chihiro confessed to Oishi-san.
That receptionist confessed to Oishi-san?!
That's what I heard.
There's also Maki-san from accounting, right?
What? Really?
"Sharing a drink with my senior whom I respect."
"Sake relaxes both of our hearts."
"He also has his own past."
"Everyone lives while hiding those scars."
"In this big city of Tokyo."
"Asai Yuki."
That's too much, Asai-san.
What?
That person is something else.
Yeah.
Oishi-san is a difficult person to understand.
I see, thank you for the information.
Yahoo!, Google and Asai-san.
Don't say that.
You...
Excuse me.
Yeah.
[Chihiro the receptionist and Maki from accounting, both of them confessed to Oishi-san.]
[He turned them down.]
[Oishi-san is currently single.]
[He turned down all mixer invitations.]
[Even though he's single, he turned down all invitations, what a serious person.]
[Does that mean that work is more important than love for him?]
[It seems like 3 years ago he was dumped by his then girlfriend whom he dated for a long time.]
[He was quite sad at the time.]
Did she got her heart broken?
It's better than a prolonged and deep scar.
Okay then, I'm going to lend her my ear so she can complain as much as she wants.
That's sexual harassment.
That's power harassment.
I can't even ask what my subordinate's troubles in this Reiwa era.
Poison.
Komukai.
Let's get trendy!
What?
He turned down all mixer invitations even though he's single.
He got his heart broken 3 years ago.
Do you think that he still has feelings for his ex?
That is a big possibility.
Do you have any information about her?
Her name is Kita Hinami.
She was Oishi-san's classmate in college,
she is the only daughter of Kakitsubata, a sake brewer.
She opened a sake bar 3 years ago.
Didn't Oishi-san always drink sake?
Maybe that is because of his ex girlfriend.
I can't see her face.
I wonder what kind of person she is.
You want to know?
First things first is know your enemy.
Isn't learning about her scary?
I want to know.
It's scary after all...
What is it?
You're going to the sake bar, aren't you?
You don't have to come with me.
This is for Riko-san's sake.
Don't get too comfortable.
Riko-san is...
She's great don't you think?
Analyze it!
Welcome.
Please enjoy yourselves.
She's so cool.
Is she the owner of this bar?
She doesn't look like she got many holes, not cute.
This is great, it's so annoying.
A well proportioned beauty.
Impeccable.
She is the type of person who looks down on others without realizing it
The sales of this sake is quite good.
Maybe she's too perfect that she loses all interest in love or other people?
I feel bad for her.
Riko-san is far from perfect, so I'm at ease.
Who's ally are you again?
Riko-san.
What?
-Why do you say that?
This is your first time here, right?
That's right.
The Kaika is delicious.
I'm happy to hear that.
My father and I made that sake.
You sure are a good child.
The scent...
Excuse me.
My senior at work, Oishi-san, told me about this place.
What? Oishi?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
At first I thought that you were an annoying perfectionist.
That's terrible.
Apology accepted.
But if that were your personality, the world is bugged.
Because I behave like this, people say that I'm a lonely or iron owner,
but it's not like that at all.
I thought that she's pretty, but she's actually cute, don't you think so?
Oishi-san is a mysterious person.
Which part of him is mysterious?
He's just a normal man.
He's our company's ace, in other words, he's a Gundam employee.
Gundam?
Gundam.
What?
He's a workaholic, right?
That is super unfortunate.
Is he a man that makes women cry?
Not at all.
In the end, he looks the best when he is working.
I also fell for him.
What is your dream again, Nakano-san?
Being a rich person.
So cute.
We won't lose to you.
That's cheating.
Was that also part of your plan?
What?
He's sleeping.
Nakano-san.
Don't tell Oishi that I said hello, okay?
What?
What happened between us is in the past.
He surprisingly has his flaws, but please continue to support him.
Okay.
Another round please!
Good morning.
Are you guys okay?
I was supposed to scout, but ended up drinking to much.
The mummy catcher became a mummy...
How did it go?
Their relationship ended a long time ago.
What was she like?
She was of medium height and had no distinctive features.
Maybe Oishi-san is someone who does not have any preference when it comes to appearance.
Doesn't have any preference?
Riko.
It's hard to say, but...
-Nakano-san.
As for her personality, she's a workaholic.
She loved her work more than Oishi-san.
She's like an AI that lacks emotion...
-Shinji!
Stop it, it's too much.
But...
To tell you the truth, she's a really pretty person,
but after I talked to her, I found that she was a really cute person.
Is that so?
If anything...
We became friends...
What a cute person.
She's a wonderful person.
Riko...
There is nothing to compare.
I want to be cute.
Did you open the wrong door?
This is a plastic model shop, Zakunee!
I want to be cute!
If you want to be something, you have to learn about it first.
There's only one option if you want to learn about cuteness.
The picture in your head is a map.
You won't reach your goal if your map is unclear.
You can picture it once you have built this.
A girl?
She's Minami Kotori.
Kotori-chan?
You don't know about Love Live!, Zakunee?
A friend of mine was really into it.
Magazines, animes and movies.
They also performed at the Tokyo Dome.
They also performed at Kouhaku, truly a legendary piece of work.
Otonokizaka Gakuin was on the verge of consolidation due to a decrease in the number of applicants.
In order to increase the number of applicants, the students of
Otonokizaka Gakuin voluntarily formed a 9-member School Idol, μ's.
Minami Kotori is one of the members of the group.
Her dream is to study fashion in the future, and she is in charge of the group's wardrobe.
So cute.
She doesn't have any self-confidence, so in order to change that, she worked part-time at a maid cafe.
She immediately became famous after she sang during an event,
people call her the legendary maid Minalinsky.
She wants to have confidence in herself, that alone makes me want to support her.
Teach me all about cuteness, Kotori-chan.
Open the box.
So scary.
Grotesque.
There is no such thing as "cute" from the start.
Quickly let all the parts out.
Forgive me, Kotori-chan.
Alright.
This looks so real.
I have a feeling that it's going to be cute.
Scary.
She's born.
The striking blush on the cheeks is created by a technique called layered injection.
The shining eyes have rounded iris edges to reproduce the blurring effect found in the original work.
Be careful.
Kotori-chan doesn't have any rough edges.
No rough edges.
So cute.
That's correct, Zakunee!
That's correct!
A quiz?
Someone who doesn't get excited by the softness of the 3 layered lace won't be a cute person.
So cute.
Good work.
Minami Kotori, give...
Riko-san!
You can do anything to achieve cuteness.
You're free to do anything with plastic model and to achieve cuteness.
Cuteness is infinite.
It's in the parts that are hard to see that cuteness resides in.
The protagonist that is late to the party, Big Stone Victory Magnum.
Big Stone?
Big stone.
This is it.
Being cute is your intention.
That's it!
Last one...
I see...
So cute.
Good job.
Love Live! Minami Kotori-chan.
Give birth!
Welcome to world of cuteness, Riko-san
Did your heart flutter?
Yes.
The more parts that I assembled, the amount of cuteness was also increased.
You won't be cute in just one day.
I thought that I can be cute immediately.
When you quickly become something,
you will be bored with it as quickly.
I'm going to add it day-by-day.
Kotori-chan,
I can be cute, can I?
[Big Stone Investigation HQ]
[Department 3 Lunch Search Party]
[Please let me treat the two of you to lunch today]
Alright, it starts today.
Morning.
Good morning.
Good work.
Huh?
Komukai-san.
Why did you revert back to your old self?
It seemed like you were about to come up with an aggressive project...
If you have the time to worry about someone else...
I didn't revert back to my old self, Asai.
Look.
You don't see that I added something?
Who knows?
Anyway, the way that you looked yesterday was better.
Don't you agree, Oishi-san?
Well, I think...
I think that you also look good today, Komukai-san.
Okay then, let's go.
Okay.
He said that I look good, right?
Yes.