masssterchief
I'm really glad that the sports car presentation was a success
Agreed
You're working really hard lately, Riko
I wonder...
You took a loan or something?
That is your conclusion?
Is there any other reason than money to work hard?
It's probably....
It's all thanks to this
Plastic model?
I was able to concentrate
It's like a brain detox
You're amazing, Ooishi-san
Yeah, I hope that you can be just as capable as me
Of course, my goal is to become the next ace of Department 1
Do your best
Takagi Shinji is gone and the department is not noisy anymore
Shinji is really dumb, don't you think so?
His brain is the only thing that seems good
No, he's dumb
What do you want for lunch?
I want to eat chilled Chinese noodles
That sounds great
Who was responsible for transferring him to Department 3?
Does it matter?
I heard rumors that it was your doing
Is that so?
Good morning
What are you drinking?
Warm water
I don't remember you being this conscious
Is drinking warm water equals high conscious?
Yes
Maybe being in Department 1 was too soon for him
Asai!
Shinji...
Good work
Oh, good work
How is Shinji doing in Department 3?
Don't push dumb people to Department 3
You got it all wrong, Nakano-san
Komukai, you better give Shinji proper guidance
If there's something that I need to do, then I'll do it
Okay, I leave Shinji in your care, Komukai-san
Of course
Please take good care of him too, Nakano-san
Okay
Your friend always get on my nerves
Is Ooishi-san always kind to everyone?
The person who is kind to everyone is usually a psycho, be careful
Shinji, what are you doing?
Have you submitted your proposal?
Don't you know, Nakano-san?
Walking is better to get oxygen into the brain
Walk for the rest of your life
Ooishi-san sure is handsome
The person in charge of the Interacting with Manten-kun event is Shinji!
Wait just a second
I absolutely can't do it
Everyone knows Manten Nodoame better than me
It's not a good idea to take unnecessary risk
Someone who understands the inner workings of Department 3 is the most important thing
Above all else, I never had Manten Nodoame before
Have you been trained to think of reasons why you can't do it?
Just do it
Don't say it like that, Saruwatari-kun
Acting Chief Kijimura, please tell the Chief the same thing
Chief Inuzuka's decision is absolute
Thank you very much
Shinji-kun, we're busy with planning the biggest event of the year that will take place in a month, Manten-kun's birthday celebration
This meeting is full with things that can be improved
This is so unproductive
What do you think, Komukai?
I think that Shinji-kun is amazing, being able to decline a project means that he's passionate
Yes, he's amazing
Can you support Shinji on this project?
Okay
Saruwatari, go teach Shinji the ropes
I can't do it because I'm swamped with other projects
Have you been trained to think of reasons why you can't do it?
Just do it
Okay
I'll be in your care
This place sure is peaceful
That's right
It's not like I don't want to be the person in charge
The right person in the right place, or rather, I'm good taking the support role and analyzing data
But, you're going to do it, right?
Yes
What?
Please tell me what to do
I'm here to support you
You're my senior, Riko-san
You're the leader, Shinji-kun
Let's start by choosing the venue, because it's a big expenditure...
Is that right?
Yes...
I can't believe that I missed the normal time to go home....
I'm sorry for not finishing in time
It's okay
It's fine
Is the proposal that we came up with is okay?
First of all, it's great that we even came up with something
Is it okay to send the data to Saruwatari-san?
There's no need to send me the data
Did you wait for us?
I was just tidying up the place
Show me
Okay
The numbers are all over the place
It's our first draft
It's not even good enough to be called that
Please be more specific then
Don't you think so?
Good work
Is now the time to go home?
It's way past the normal time to go home
Good work
He ignored me
We have used this venue before
The venue is close from the train station and attracts a large number of visitors,
so we expect many families to come to the event
What should we do next?
What? I'll leave that to you
Should we go the shopping district and ask to put up posters for the event?
We haven't made the script to explain the event to the MC too
As my support, I want you to schedule things for us
Look
What is that?
It's close from here, what do you think?
You're too punctual, Riko-san
Lunch is decided then
Why is it like this?
The budget for the lighting for the venue is way off the mark
I'm sorry
Please
Do we have a place to put it on?
I don't mind where you put it on, please put Manten-kun up
She said that Manten-kun will come
What about over there
Really?
He said it's okay
Thank you very much
I'm following Manten Nodoame's official account
Mikiki-san
I love your song "Ganbare Semiko-san"
I'm so happy to hear that
As I told you before, if you try to fudge up the numbers, it will get found out eventually
Understood
Thank you very much
Are you listening, Shinji?
I'm taking notes
Click clack click clack
I'm sure that you're working on something different
That's unforgivable
Please take a look
Nope
Well well welll
Let's see it
Okay
He's dumb, you know?
He's motivated, but maybe it's because there's a gap between him and the job
I can't do it
There's Kijimura behind Manten
Ask me anything
Saruwatari-san, does he has a loose screw or something?
I didn't expect you to be a strong drinker, Shinji
I don't hate alcohol
Have you had a drink with Saruwatari?
There's no way
What about with Komukai-san?
No
You should just go and ask them
I can't do it
It's a piece of cake
Should I order something expensive to cheer you up?
Just say to them "Please take me somewhere"
"Please take me somewhere"
That's quite a hard thing to say
Should I order some sea urchins?
Is Saruwatari-san good at his job?
Hey, it's only been an hour since we started drinking
Well well
He's the up and coming generation after all
You're right
Cheers to youth
Cheers
Have you heard something about Shinji from Komukai-san?
I'm not close with that mass production type employee
What? Looking at your attitude towards her,
I thought that the two of you are childhood friends or something
Please don't say such a thing
The rumor is that Shinji is butting heads with Saruwatari-san
Riko-san
You're a dry person, aren't you?
What?
You have to be joking
I'm about to die because it's so out of left field
How do I put it...
The people in Department 1 are more passionate
I'll do it when the time comes
Are you working seriously?
I'm going to say it because you started it
Stop using your laptop all the time
I want you to step forward even more, because you're the leader after all
I was the only one who said something to the client during the meeting
I was also the only one who negotiated putting up the posters
You're using your laptop as a shield to avoid risks
Laptop shield...
It's like you're not all in on the project
I was just wrapping my head around it while taking notes
My goal is to analyze those notes later
I leave Shinji in your care, Komukai-san
My goal is to perfectly support you, so don't worry!
Yes?
You can say anything to me
Well, please...
Please?
Please...
Please take me somewhere
Somewhere? Where?
Anywhere is fine, as long as it's a place that you often go to
Somewhere that I often to go...
Please take me there
What am I looking at?
It's beautiful, don't you agree?
Yes
Don't say that, we're not going to a bar?
What? So that is what you meant?
Welcome
I'm happy that you came back for more
More?
It's a large serving this time
Is he your boyfriend?
What is this place?
A model shop
Is he your boyfriend, Zaku-nee?
Zaku-nee?
I'm touched that you brought someone here with you
Is he your boyfriend?
He's my junior at work, Takagi Shinji-kun
Why plastic models though?
Because it's fun
You know how it's going to look like in the end
They purposely took it apart and then you have to build it yourself, which takes a lot of time and effort, I just can't understand it
Try saying that after you have built one
Try building one, Shinji-kun
Don't you think that it's a waste of time?
Build this
Evangelion
Your name is Shinji, right?
Yay!
I'm busy, you know?
You're handsome, Shinji-san
What?
I don't have any choice then
Evangelion Unit 01
I have watched the show before
Okay then, open the box
Okay
Open the box
The runners are colorful
You can finish building it without using any paint
I don't understand it all
Don't worry, he will teach you all about it
Evangelion
Everyone has heard of it before
The gold standard of anime
It originally aired in 1995, it became a huge social phenomenon that involves even people who don't watch anime
It happened before I was born
It was relaunched in 2007 with an all new movie
The final movie that was released last year was an unprecedented hit
It is truly a masterpiece that will live on in history
I watched the first and second movies
That is the All-Purpose Humanoid Decisive Battle Weapon Artificial Human Evangelion Unit 01
It is the Eva that the main character, Shinji, uses
There's no way that I'm going to do this all on my own, right?
There are a lot of runners
You're going to do this alone
Is it okay for one person to build it?
He's going to do it alone
You can do it, Shinji-san
I'm going to do it all by myself
Do your best
It's going to be a piece of cake, I have the instruction manual after all
You're amazing, Shinji-san
That instruction manual is the coolest thing ever
You need a lot of patience to complete this plastic model
But, your name is Shinji-kun
I think that you should just do it without running away from it
Let's get started
I feel like this is going to take a lot of time
Just take it easy
You're good at using the nipper
It looks a bit rough
This is too much
Just stop if you feel like it
I was just resting my hands
It's not a robot
What?
Evangelions are man-made humans
That's why even the smallest muscles are reproduced
The large number of parts allows for a high degree of reproducibility
It's not a robot
It is alive
I have changed my mind about it
Huh?
The parts that you didn't look at closely doesn't fit
This is the problem
Being meticulous is important
I'll teach you how to cut it again next time
All right
It's not good to have a plastic models with gaps within them
You should push it in more
Don't be scared! Push!
It's in
Nice
How was it?
It felt like something got inside of me too
All right
Should I give you a hand?
What are you saying right now?
It looks like it's going to take a while
Don't worry about the shop
I'm grateful for that, but...
Please let me do this on my own
But...
Let's proceed, Yassan
Go for it, Shinji!
Okay
Nice
Go, Shinji-san
It looks so cool
Nice
The next step is the hands, you can choose from a number of different variations
Bare hands, open hands, clenched fists, pallet rifles and even Progressive Knife
You can do it, Shinji-san
I'm going with clenched fists
All right
Evangelion Unit 01
Give birth!
-Give birth?!
I'm sorry that I fell asleep
You look happy
It's because I finished it on my own
You did well
I saw the view from the front line for the first time
Evangelion is so beautiful
Congratulations
Thank you very much
Riko-san
I want to get back to work
Okay, let's do our best
Shinji-san
Yes?
We used to drink together a lot back in the day, didn't we?
You hated it, didn't you?
Not at all, I was proud that I got to share a drink with the ace of Department 1
What a response
How is Shinji doing?
It was your doing after all huh?
He looks just like me when I first joined the company
I wanted him to learn from you, Saru-san
There was an event today
We're back
Did everything went smoothly?
I thought that it was exciting
But, we recorded a loss
I was too naive with a lot of things
That's not a surprise
The loss was within our expectation
Thank you for covering for his mistake
Being tasked as a leader for this project
I keenly felt that I had not taken a step forward until now
By taking on more responsibility, I was able to see many areas for improvement
The first thing is...
Make it quick
Well...
Working hard is worth it
Sit down
Okay
I want to hear from the two of you
Thank you very much
Okay
He's finally at the starting line
I was just watching over him this time
Saru-san
Why don't you come back to Department 1?
I can talk to the higherups
I don't have that kind of passion anymore
Welcome
Come here
Shinji
Don't you dare open your laptop