masssterchief
What is this place?
My name is Asai Yuki, 23 years old.
I'm in my 3rd year working at a small to medium sized event planning company, I'm a promising employee.
I had dinner for the first time with my colleague Riko, but...
Why am I building a plastic model???
Congratulations for getting the CEO award.
It's all thanks to you, Oishi-san.
I'm just happy to see a new events department member has improved so much.
Of course.
Department 3 is also doing well.
You look so happy.
Excuse me, another round of lemon sour please.
What about you, Oishi-san?
Have you heard about it?
Could it be that I'm getting promoted?
No, about Department 3 getting dissolved.
Are you joking?
I wouldn't joke about such a thing.
No...
Please wait just a second.
Lately Department 3 is looking like a real team,
don't you think that it's wrong?
Agreed.
It's too bad.
Can't we do anything about it?
At the very least, I won't be making a move.
Don't you think that's a bit harsh?
Aren't you close with the members of Department 3?
I have my reasons.
If Department 3 is dissolved,
what will happen to them?
They will be on different departments,
or maybe some of them will leave the company.
That is not right!
They made this decision based on their performance.
I will go talk to the higher ups.
I won't stop you, but I can't give you my support.
If give a proper explanation, surely the higher ups will understand.
In the end, they don't know anything about what's going on in the field.
You sure are confident.
I'm the company's next ace.
I will be aggressive.
The actual survey results shows that there is a high demand for actually experiencing it themselves.
As I have just explained, the nature of events department is undergoing a major shift.
That was well put together.
Thank you very much.
Okay then, let's wrap it up.
That was impressive.
May I have a moment of everyone's time?
If Department 3 is dissolved, it will have a repercussion for Department 1 and 2.
I think that is the best solution for everyone involved.
Above all, it is imperative that we establish a new digital department.
If anything, the whole events department needs to be expanded.
It's the time to be aggressive!
I'm glad that the Mirai Expo event was a success.
I agree.
Thank you very much.
Don't thank me, thank Manten-sama.
From now on, I will not keep things to myself.
We don't have any major events in the works, so let's take it easy.
Okay.
What are you talking about?
It's nothing.
I see.
Komukai.
Oishi is leaving the company.
What?
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry, it's nothing.
I see.
Why is he leaving?
He's going to the biggest company in the industry.
He's so good at his job after all.
Why are you telling me this?
It's clear as day.
What should I do?
Well, I can't do anything about it though.
Anyway, do your best, Komukai!
Okay.
You're so motivated, Shinji.
I'm thinking about whether I should confess or not.
What?
-To Chiemi-chan?
She's the only one for me.
I thought that you already confessed to her.
I'm not confident at all.
Confessing your love without any confidence is unthinkable.
That's right, could it be that you're in the same boat, Riko?
You're going to confess, Riko-san?
Finally to Oishi-san.
It's finally that time, huh.
I don't have any confidence nor there's a possibility to succeed, so it's impossible.
I feel the same way.
You said that you wanted to get cuter for Oishi-san's sake?
Listen Nakano-san,
that and confessing are two different things.
Why are you assuming that I never confessed my love before?
I'm sorry.
Is it even a confession if you know there's a chance to succeed?
You're being weird, Nakano-san.
I think that it's a bother to receive a love confession from someone that you don't like.
Totally.
It's impossible for me to confess.
Have you confessed your love to someone before, Nakano-san?
No.
Isn't that a bit unfair?
What is?
Well...
What?
It's all too sudden.
Totally.
What are you going to do, Komukai?
What? You know?
Yeah.
It's clear as day, huh?
I'm so ashamed.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
Be confident.
Okay.
But there's nothing that I can do.
I'm going to help you out, so do your best until the end.
What? Why are you doing this?
It doesn't concern me, but I don't want it to end like this.
Asai...
I mean...
Don't you want to change?
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Alright.
I can't afford to lose.
I'm getting nervous.
Let's do it!
Yeah!
I'm terribly sorry.
Don't do something like that ever again.
Understood.
Excuse me.
So, the proposal that you presented out of the blue during the board meeting didn't come to anything?
Where did you hear that from?
I did something similar before.
You should have stopped me.
I won't do such a thing.
Are you giving up?
Of course not.
But...
You understand that passion alone is not enough, right?
Are you talking about the numbers?
There's a chance for Department 3 to survive if they won a big competition.
But, can I find such a perfect competition right now?
Is our line of work exclusive to the private sector?
Thank you very much.
Good work.
Yes.
He's working hard.
He's the pride and joy of our class.
Oishi-san?
He's working hard for your sake.
What?
Excuse me.
Good work.
Komukai!
Morning.
I may have found a breakthrough.
Really?
Yes, just wait a little bit longer.
Hey, did Oishi-san said something to you?
He gave me some advice.
What? Are you an idiot?
That's unthinkable.
Just how prideful are you?
We have to get a result this time, by any means necessary.
Am I wrong?
You're right, but...
Rest assured, I can do it.
What are you doing?
This won't affect my work.
Asai.
You're getting transferred next month.
What?
To the digital department?
Please wait a second...
To HR.
HR?
There's someone who is on paternity leave.
It's an important department.
Me in HR?
What?
I got the CEO award the other day...
Look around you.
Everyone here has won the CEO award.
Komukai.
Asai.
What's wrong?
Want to grab something to eat?
Oh.
Okay.
It feels like...
It feels like I lost all of my strength in an instant.
You couldn't stop Oishi-san from leaving after all, huh?
What?
Don't worry about me.
I feel bad for making you help me.
Oishi-san is leaving the company?
What?
You don't know?
No, I don't. When did you tell me?
I told you at the rooftop.
We were talking about the dissolvement of Department 3, right?
What? Department 3 is getting dissolved?
Wait wait wait.
There's no way that you didn't know.
No I don't. Is that the truth?
Yes.
What about Oishi-san?
I heard it from Saruwatari-san.
Seriously?
What about you supporting me to confess my love?
To who?
Oishi-san.
Oishi...
Do you like Oishi-san?
I'm thinking about confessing before he leaves the company.
My head can't keep up with all of this.
So what's going to happen to us working at Department 3?
As you said, I can't give up on Department 3.
That's my colleague.
What about you?
For the company...
I'm nothing...
It must be hard on you to be told that out of the blue.
Did my passion count for nothing?
Asai...
Do you remember that you told me that I'm a mass-production type person?
I was annoyed back then.
My bad.
You know.
Asai.
You're also a mass-production type person.
What?
Don't pick a fight at a time like this.
I'm not picking a fight with you.
I'm going to pay for all of this,
so I want you to follow me tonight.
Thanks for waiting.
Yeah.
Asai.
Komukai.
He's my colleague.
He works hard for the company.
But a lot of things happened yesterday.
I felt a lot better after building plastic models here with you and Chiemi-chan.
Why am I building a plastic model?
Err...
I'm sober now.
You were focused.
Err...
You don't remember? I'm Yassan.
I'm Chiemi.
I'm Riko.
I know.
Gundam?
Thank you for following me.
Are you going to continue?
Well...
I promised her after she paid for all the sake.
Actually, I was also an office worker back in the day.
He quit his job and then started this shop.
Is that so?
Let's get started.
We'll deal with the rough spots as we work our way through the gates!
A 400 smoother.
You're going to smooth out the left over gates.
Okay.
I'm motivated now.
Roger that.
If so, then I'm off!
This is the first time this year that he's this serious.
This time, you use glue in the beginning to remove the seam.
Apply to both sides of the part and press firmly.
What do you think?
That's fine.
Thank you very much.
You should use more glue here.
Here?
Okay.
If you have confirmed that the glue is all dried up,
it's time to remove the excess glue.
Alright.
it's time to paint them.
But before that, let's wash them first!
Wash?
The surface of the parts are covered with hand grease and release agent.
Start!
Next up, is to paint the undercoat.
It's a process called surfacer.
It is used to fill in fine scratches, eliminate unevenness in color and improve the adhesion of the paint.
What do you think?
Good.
Okay.
Please take this.
If you find a flaw, smooth it out.
Okay.
You're going to paint it again afterwards.
You're free to use any color.
Tone it any way you want.
Okay.
You can airbrush it if you want.
Looking good.
Perfect.
Next.
Use ink for the lines.
Okay.
Do this part too.
Alright.
Finally, do this one.
All of it?
That's right.
Go for it!
Okay.
You have a lot of enemies.
I'm going to do it all.
Keep going.
Do you want to take a break?
No, I can still do it.
You can do it.
Get rid of the shine!
Okay.
Alright, next.
Next please.
Alright.
Huh?
This is not a Gundam?
High Grade RGM-79 'GM'.
Although it has been more than 20 years since its release,
the proportions are still convincing even when assembled today.
As a mass-production type mobile suit, you won't get bored no matter how much you build them.
It's still being supported by the fans to this day, truly a famous kit.
GM...
GM was developed based on operational data from the Gundam.
Based on the design of the Gundam, but
by eliminating the expensive mechanism and lowering the cost
it became a mass-produced mobile suit that boasted overwhelming production power and was used by the Earth Federation Forces.
The specs are on par with those of the Principality of Zeon's mobile suits.
It looks similar, but...
It's not a Gundam, but a mass-production mobile suit?
I was surprised when I found this GM the other day.
Other than Zaku, there are another mass-produced mobile suit in the Gundam universe called GM.
Young man.
It's the last part.
Okay.
I'm the next ace.
I'm going to be aggressive.
My goal is to become the next ace.
Work using your own name.
Am I getting promoted?
It's time to be aggressive.
Rest assured, I can do it.
Asai. You're getting transferred next month.
HR?
I'm not close to that mass-production type employee.
I got the CEO award the other day.
Since when you become a mass production-type person?
Give birth!
Good job finishing it.
Asai.
This GM...
Is me.
I believed from the bottom of my heart that I was a Gundam.
But today for the first time...
I feel like I properly saw my own face.
The body of a Gundam.
But the head is a GM.
I'm a GM of the company,
that can be easily replaced.
If I'm a Zaku,
then you're a GM.
Even if I'm currently a GM,
I want to be a Gundam.
I thought that being a mass-production type person is okay.
You can freely customize your life.
I love Department 3,
I don't want it to get dissolved, so I'll do my best.
I think that if Department 3 managed to get this, there's a chance that it will survive.
It's a COOL JAPAN event competition in Singapore.
There's still time to make it.
Asai...
This is all that I can do.
You do the rest.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
I'm still in shock about Oishi-san.
Oh yeah.
Can I still count on your support for me confessing to him?
I told you that was a misunderstanding.
I see.
You have a surprisingly egregious personality, don't you?
Which part?
Nope.