masssterchief
Good morning.
Nakano, let's have a drink after work.
I have to pass.
Did you drank too much last night?
Is that the only reason for me to turn down your invitation?
You seemed pretty busy lately.
Not at all.
If you need any help, just say the word.
I can still make it in time.
That means that Nakano haven't fully trusted you just yet.
That's not true. Lately the way that she calls my name is filled with love.
She always say your name with the same tone.
Department 3 is also peaceful today.
What about you, Saruwatari-san?
She looks at me with respect. Ask me anything about horse racing.
Asai from Department 1 is amazing, I heard that he got another project.
He's the next ace for sure.
Did you hear about it? It seems like our company has begun restructuring.
It wasn't a rumor?
The overseas sales department was dissolved.
I heard that the event department will also be abolished.
I guess the department with the worst sales is on the chopping block.
Well, our department should be fine.
But, Department 3 is in a pinch, right?
If things keep up like this...
Morning everyone.
Good morning.
I just have to do it.
Thank you for the other day.
I had no idea that Nakano-san, whom I met at a bar, was from an event company.
I thought that you were just hitting on me.
I'm here to talk business.
Home medical equipment?
That's right.
We're still a new start-up company
but we want to set up a big booth at the upcoming Mirai Expo.
That Mirai Expo?
The one at Makuhari?
That's right.
Because it attracts a lot of attention from the media, we would like to show off our products there.
I see.
But, we don't have much time left.
Is it too hard to pull off?
No, I'll do it.
Let's do it.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
A chance to comeback from the dead.
Alright.
Good work.
Overtime?
Yeah...
Nakano-san, it's the most pointless time in our lives.
I take back what I said.
Komukai, don't bother Nakano!
I'm not bothering her at all.
What are you working on? A new proposal?
Inuzuka-san, don't bother her.
I only asked her a question!
Don't overdo it, okay?
Okay.
Good work.
I want the booth to look like this.
Is white the main color?
That's right, it's simple, but I want it to look stylish.
I want this monitor to display a video promoting the products.
Something that packs a punch, right?
I want it to stand out from the other booths.
I'm going to think about the content ASAP.
Thank you very much.
About the Mirai Expo booth space,
I have secured the desired spot.
I'm afraid we're a little over budget on the booth decorations,
but I'll try to keep it within the total budget.
That's right, I'll have it before the end of the day.
Alright, the estimation is done.
Nakano-san?
3 minutes has passed.
Thanks.
What is it?
You have bags under your eyes.
Seriously?
This is the worst.
Did you get 8 hours of sleep?
I never slept for that long to begin with.
How do I put it, you're unusual, Nakano-san.
What?
You can finish your work on your own,
I think that you can work even harder.
You're asking why am I in the laid back Department 3?
Our department is comfortable, though.
People can tell if you're capable or not.
That's the kind of thing that builds trust with the client!
We don't have to always run as fast as possible in life, right?
If jogging is comfortable, then so be it.
Totally.
But, I have to do it right now.
What? What do you mean?
We couldn't get funding from investors as much as we wanted.
What happens with Mirai Expo then?
All the budget that we hoped for is all gone.
That's...
We have booked the space and have begun the production.
I want to cancel everything.
It's not that easy to cancel...
I'm very sorry.
We're just a start-up company after all.
A start-up company...
That's all, please excuse me.
You have got to be kidding me.
This is not good.
This is it.
You're going to give this to Chiemi-chan for her birthday?
It's to celebrate her 20th birthday.
Don't you think that this is too heavy?
I don't want her to question my taste by giving her common bath products.
Bath products is okay.
Oh yeah.
You're impartial.
I'll take this.
Which one do you think is better, Nakano-san?
What? Either one is good.
Which one?
Either one is fine.
I'm Chiemi-chan...
This one is a big no.
What do you mean by that?
Which one should I pick then?
Either one is fine! Think about it yourself!
What?
I'm sorry.
Nakano-san?
What's wrong?
We're back.
Good work.
Huh? Where is Nakano-san?
She told me this morning that she's going to take the day off.
Taking the day off?
Maybe she has a bad hangover?
This is the first time that Nakano is taking some time off since she came to Department 3.
She wasn't part of Department 3 since the beginning?
No, she was reassigned here just like you.
Is that so?
The department that she was originally assigned to is called the newbie destroyer.
All the seniors around her was cold to her,
they didn't teach her anything about her job at all.
That's terrible.
And them, Chief Inuzuka found her crying in the smoking area,
and asked her to join his department, am I right?
Is that so?
I just can't leave a crying kitten alone.
Her style of not relying on others, started from way back then, right?
My opinion of Nakano-san has changed 180 degrees.
How did you see Nakano-san before?
Even though she's like that, she loves this department.
20 million in damages is bad.
Do I have to take responsibility...
Or change jobs...
[Do you want me to bring you Pocari and jelly?]
[Did something happened?]
[No.]
[If you're fine, then let's have dinner.]
Why are you here?
I heard that you wanted me to come.
There's no way.
Now that I think about it, it's wrong.
Don't you think the three of us hanging out together is great?
I'm fine with this.
Why did you took the day off all of the sudden?
Let's see, because I felt like it?
I admire that strong will.
Saruwatari-san, can you prepare the materials for tomorrow?
I'm in that kind of mood.
It's impossible for me.
Please say something will you? Like "Are you an idiot?".
Shut up.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much?
I'm going to take some.
Please rely on me more will you.
Well, maybe you thought I was quite crazy at first, but
I've made improvements after improvements and now I've become a capable person...
Shinji-kun is like this after just 2 rounds?
He's like this after an hour.
He gets drunk according to the time?
It's new, isn't it?
Nakano-san.
Do you want to go to another place?
Okay.
So unusual.
Is this THE plastic model shop?
This is the oasis that I found in the city.
This is also my love nest with Chiemi-chan.
I'll have to pass.
Wait just a second.
You've come all the way here.
I have no interest in plastic models at all.
Everyone says that at the beginning.
Pardon our intrusion.
Good evening.
Welcome.
Is she your friend?
I'm her colleague, Nakano.
I heard stories about you from Zakunee, Nakano-san.
Chiemi-chan?
I also heard stories about you from Shinji.
Shinji-san?
Not another word, Nakano-san.
Is this your first time?
First time?
This is your first time building a plastic model, right?
What?
I said that I'm good.
What do you like? Gundam? Evangelion? Love Live!? Ultraman?
I loved Ultraman.
I didn't mean that I want to build one.
He's already searching for it.
What?
Ultraman.
It's different from the Ultraman that I know.
It looks modern.
This Ultraman is set several decades after the well-known tokusatsu series Ultraman produced by Tsuburaya Productions.
It doesn't connect to the larger Ultraman series, just like Ultraseven.
The comic takes place in an alternate universe.
The most defining feature of this series is the Ultraman is not an alien, but a human wearing a reinforced suit.
What? He doesn't get bigger?
On top of that, that person is
a troubled high school student.
A troubled high school student.
It's actually so cool.
Do you want to try building it, Nakano-san?
No, thank you.
Don't say that.
This is your hobby, right?
It's the hobby of everyone in Deparment 3.
Preparation is complete.
I may not look like it, but I'm actually clumsy.
I'm well aware, I sit right next to you everyday after all.
I may put the arms and legs backwards.
That's why we're going to build this together.
Together?
Is that even allowed?
You can do anything with plastic models.
Okay then, let's do it.
Do it?
What?
Here we go, ready...
Open the box.
I take it all out?
Please do.
It's more detailed than I imagined.
Riko-san.
That's right, let's do that at the start.
Do what?
Yes.
You're also painting the runners today, huh?
This is possible because each runner are different colors.
Riko, you never showed that look before at work.
I'm going to be quiet.
Alright.
You paint red for the red parts, Nakano-san.
Red for the red parts.
That's right.
You use silver for the silver parts.
Alright, it's all dried up.
Okay then, let's get started.
Alright.
Please build the torso, Nakano-san.
I'll build the legs and Shinji will build the arms.
Roger that.
Your way of doing things is scary.
She has become a proper senior.
You look so happy, Yassan.
Where should I start cutting?
G7.
Number 7 is this one.
Please cut it from the bottom.
From the bottom?
-Yes.
Wait! Where are you going to cut it?
It doesn't matter where I cut it, right?
No, you were going to cut it's waist, you know?
Waist?
What? How much of all of these is the waist?
What is it?
No, you're getting attacked.
Nakano-san, don't panic and just take it slow.
I'm not panicking.
Okay okay.
May I?
Yes.
Err...
Did I made a mistake?
-Not at all.
Please cut the part where it still has the remains of the gate one more time.
It's called second cut.
Second cut?
Where is the B runner?
It's this one.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Where is it?
Which one is it?
It's this one.
I see.
Don't force it!
What?
Please do it more gently.
Gently?
Gently...
Here you go.
Thanks.
What a nice sound.
It's done.
This feels so good.
Look at this.
It has a wide range of motion.
I can't put it in at all.
It's no good if you force it.
Flexibility and strength are the essence of building plastic models.
Okay.
I did it.
Evertything good?
Yes.
It looks like a real joint.
Because there are ball joints inside the chest and waist,
that allows the figure to have a wide range of motion and so you can make it do all kinds of poses.
Alright, let's proceed.
Okay.
I wonder what Ultraman looks like.
What's with you all of the sudden?
I can't tell if it's crying, laughing or angry.
Now that you mention it, it's kinda sad.
He is a lone warrior who does not show any expressions.
Isn't it a little too much of an act of selfless love to protect the earth by yourself?
If it were me, I would want to be adored by all human beings.
That is the fate of a hero.
Don't you think that it's easier to do anything with others?
I can't handle being alone.
Me too.
Please proceed, Riko-san.
Okay
Nakano-san.
Here you go.
What?
Thanks.
It's your job to assemble it, Nakano-san.
Okay.
It's done.
Alright, it's decide the pose.
Okay.
Ultraman, give birth!
Give birth?
That is how we do things.
The Specium Beam is so amazing.
The way the knees bend, it's amazing!
It's the magic of range of motion.
It's the magic of range of motion?
The plastic model road is so deep.
Well done.
They built most of this.
It doesn't matter who did it.
I didn't expect to go to the plastic model shop with Nakano-san.
She's more clumsy that I expected, right?
She would have broke it if we let her be.
That's right.
Right?
What's wrong, Nakano-san?
Riko...
Please...
Please help me.
You took way too long to say it.
You knew?
What about me, Nakano-san?
I'll make it in time.
Actually...
WHAT??
That is beyond my imagination.
Good morning.
Morning.
Nakano-san, what do you think about this proposal?
What? Manten Nodoame Mirai Expo event?
I remembered that their President is interested in doing something like this.
I'm thinking about changing the decoration of the booth to match Manten Nodoame.
That...
Chief, I managed to secure an appointment with them.
Good job.
Appointment? We're doing to do the presentation right now?
It seems like you're relying on me.
What?
Everyone.
I'm terribly sorry.
Nakano is apologizing.
I kept it all by myself and caused trouble to Department 3.
You really haven't changed, have you?
Don't be a stranger, Nakano-san.
Alright, speed is important.
Let's go do the presentation right now.
Roger that.
Let's go, Nakano.
I'm sorry.
That was close.