masssterchief
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I guess I'm really tired.
Saru-chan, about the audition for the next Manten Girl...
You see it too, Chief?
You can see it too, Saru?
What's wrong?
Kijimura-san.
There might be a Zashiki-warashi in this place.
They say that it brings good fortune, right?
Good luck and...
Can you see it too, Kijimura-san?
Well, I'm looking at it right now.
There you are.
I told you to wait over there.
Thank you very much for your help.
Your younger brother?
-Your neighbor's child?
Your nephew?
-Your son?
My sister's son.
He's your sister's son, huh?
But why is he here?
My sister's husband got admitted into the hospital, so he was entrusted to me this morning.
He had nowhere to go, so he ended up at Department 3.
He looks like a smart Zashihki-warashi.
What is your name?
Shoma.
How old are you?
I'm 8 years old.
8 years old. Great!
Great?
Because his daughter ignores him, just by talking to him makes him happy.
Okay Shoma, I'm going to take you to a good place.
That's a red light, Komukai.
An alpha generation kid can't handle the Chief's passion.
Chief.
Where are you going?
A place where we can be the wind!
What do you think Shoma?
My Lightning Avante Jr. is cool, right?
Yes.
I'm going to build one for you, okay?
Huh?
Is he your son, Inuzuka-san?
No, he's Komukai's.
What?
You have a son?
No, he's my nephew.
I see. Of course.
I'm going to lend you mine, would you like to race with it?
That sounds good.
Okay.
I feel bad if you lend him your mini 4WD.
It's okay.
Huh? Where is Big Stone Victory Magnum?
You call it by it's full name.
I mean, you're the one who named it, right?
Nakano-san.
What are you guys doing in the middle of the day?
My boy Shoma and I are just feeling the wind.
Is he your nephew, Riko?
That's right.
Are you having fun?
Of course you're having fun, right?
Yes.
Alright, come with me.
Aren't you having fun?
That's too much, just do one line.
I didn't know that Nakano has that skill in her.
According to the data, she is the oldest out of the three siblings, so her babysitting skills is at a pro level.
Good bye my boy.
Are you crying?
He's going to be in your care for a while right? Are you going to be okay?
It's the first time that it's just the two of us, so I'm super worried.
Shoma, take good care of Riko, okay?
Okay.
Thank you very much.
I took this picture.
Look!
It's already 3 years ago, huh?
Both the 5 year old and 8 year old Shoma are so precious.
What?
Oh, did I interrupt you?
You came into my field of view.
What are you watching?
Youtube.
What video?
Anijyaotojya.
A Kabuki actor?
Gaming youtuber.
Do you play with your friends?
Of course.
Who is your best friend?
El-kun.
Is he a foreigner?
An online game friend.
Online game friend...
What is your favorite food?
Hi-Chew, the grape flavor is the best.
Really?
Do you remember that I was the one who told you that?
What?
You used to say "Please marry me Riko" while eating it.
So funny.
More importantly, what is Nakano-san like?
What?
You're changing your favorite?
She's so cool, don't you agree?
Yes.
You're right.
[Five rules to become a mother from your big sister.]
[First, let him work on his homework on his own.]
Alexa.
35 x 6 is?
210.
Wow.
You can't do that, solve it on your own.
Alexa.
27 x 53 is?
1431.
[Second, have dinner at 7 PM.]
Why are you cooking? You should just order from Uber Eats.
It's Curry Prince.
I see.
What? You like it, don't you?
That's a long time ago.
It's sweet.
I prefer green curry.
[Third, only 3 hours max of tablet use.]
It's been more than 3 hours, Shoma.
It's alright.
No, it's not.
Your mother will scold me if she finds out.
She won't find out if you don't tell her.
Am I wrong?
[Fourth, make him call his mother (me).]
-I did it all on my own.
I didn't use Alexa.
Riko was with me.
I'm going to sleep at 9, okay?
Tablet?
I didn't use it all day, not even once.
[Fifth, make him sleep at 9 PM.]
It's already past 9 PM.
It's time to go to bed.
Wait, Otojya-san is streaming right now.
You promised your mother that you're going to bed early.
I'm not sleepy.
Shoma.
Lying leads to stealing.
Riko!
You're so annoying!
What's wrong?
Please help me.
Your hair is so messy, Zakunee.
Do you have a plastic model that kids can have fun with?
Plastic model is open to everyone.
There is no age barrier.
There is an age target.
How old is the kid?
He's an 8 year old boy.
Is this...
SD Gundam BB Warrior LEGEND BB Musha Gundam.
It's a series of deformed versions of mobile suits from the Gundam series.
Deformed?
That's right.
The name "BB Warrior" comes from the gimmick of firing BB bullets mounted on the weapon.
The new version of that legendary series is called LEGEND BB Series.
It looks so cute and fun.
This is the Gundam that in the turbulent times, as the leader of the Seven Warriors, fought many battles against the Dark Legion.
It's going to strike you down if you underestimate it.
I'm going to be careful.
Have you seen my tablet, Riko?
I've hid it.
WHY?
But how?
It's super basic to hide it under the bed.
I'll take this.
How?
It was super easy to find.
Are you a child, Riko?
I couldn't find it anywhere.
This is what happens when adults get serious.
Where is it?
For you, Shoma.
What is this?
Where is my tablet?
This is a BB Gundam plastic model.
Let's build this together.
I don't want to.
Give my tablet back.
Look, it looks cute but it's actually really cool.
Cute?
Did I told you that I like those kind of things?
No.
About the curry and Hi-Chew.
When did that happen again?
Just the other day.
3 years ago?
I'm not the same person as I was back then.
You're really bad.
Shoma.
I'm sorry for making assumptions.
I haven't changed a bit in this past three years,
so I treated you just like I did back then.
But your three years is completely different, right?
Riko.
Three years is a long time.
When you became an adult,
time flies so fast looking at the same thing all the time.
It makes me a bit sad.
For you.
It's the one that I bought.
The grape flavor is the best.
We've now made up, right?
Are you an ikemen or something?
It's delicious.
So good.
What?
How do you build this?
Do you want to build it?
Yes.
Is that so?
It's so cool.
Wow.
There's something even more amazing over there, Shoma.
Don't say another word.
I can tell.
It's the eyes of someone who is shaking with amazement.
Riko...
Can I open it?
You can do anything with plastic models.
What?
As you assemble the parts, it's so exciting that I'm going to have a nose bleed.
Wow.
You can open it.
Open the box.
What in the world?
Don't mind them.
This time, there are a lot of weapons and other things with sharp tips,
so be careful and go for it!
Is this a Yari?
That is called Naginata.
It's a rifle.
Tanegashima Rifle.
It's a sword, Riko.
It's the famous sword, Bukyumaru.
You're even more amazing than usual.
Yassan even loves the name of the weapons.
I see.
Be careful, okay?
Yes.
You're so good at this.
Looking good.
I just have to build it according to this, right?
Do you want to create your own Musha Gundam?
You have to paint it if you want it to look like the real thing.
The most important thing is undercoating.
Here we go.
It's completely different from the instruction manual.
The paint battle is still ongoing.
Next up is the topcoat.
What is your favorite color, Shoma?
Black.
It's like a Musha Gundam that fell into the darkness, it gives me goosebumps.
Fell into the darkness?
That's so cool.
If you want it to look cool, imagine it in your head.
Why black?
Why did it fell into the darkness?
Someone betrayed it.
By a friend whom it once fought with?
More.
You have to be more specific.
I'm having quite the hard time.
If the one who betrayed Musha Gundam is it's own brother, it's going to be even sadder.
That's it!
Go for it, young man.
Okay.
Ready...
You're good at this.
I think that's enough.
That's it.
What a good darkness this is.
Can you do it?
It's in.
There are two heads.
Once you assemble it, you can also make it to be a foot soldier.
Foot soldier?
Infantrymen that are at the front of the army.
The simplicity of the design expresses the fleetingness and melancholy.
Well, that is...
I prefer Gundam.
You can do anything with plastic models.
It's done.
You say "Give birth" once you have completed it.
Wait.
What is this?
Gundam marker.
The battle is not over.
Young man,
if you want to make it look the coolest,
break trough the ceiling!
Inking the Kabuto gives it a more three-dimensional and realistic feel.
So detailed.
All that remains is putting on it's weapon.
Young man, take up arms!
It's time to go to battle!
Ready...
Musha Gundam, give birth!
What a wonderful sparkle.
It's so cool, right?
Thank you very much.
The future of the children is the future of plastic models.
Likewise, thank you very much.
I got a lot of notifications.
It's going viral.
What is?
You posted this online?
I sure did.
Why did you do that?
So funny.
No, it's not!
Shoma.
I'm sorry.
I have a girlfriend.
What?
I'm sorry, Riko.
8 year olds these days are peerless.
Because there is no target age for love.
Master.
Riko.
You like that Oishi person, don't you?
What? Me?
Is that so?
You're my aunt and my ex-fiancee.
It was easy to figure out.
I like Oishi-san?
How do you know?
You have the same look when looking at plastic model and him.
And also, you act weird around him.
Don't assume things about me!
What are you going to do?
I'm not going to do anything.
We work at the same company.
I'm also in the same class as my girlfriend.
I suppose so.
Adults do over think things.
For you.
What? Why?
A charm.
A charm for what?
Riko,
muster up the courage,
and take arms to Oishi, the country!
No, I won't.
Yes, you're going to do it.
No, I'm not.
Absolutely you will.
I can't.
You can do it.