masssterchief
Last Shooting.
The climax of Mobile Suit Gundam.
While the head is gone and it's all banged up,
it muster up all of its remaining strength,
and shot the Zeong above it.
You made this, didn't you?
Do you want to try and build one too?
What?
Our sales is low when compared to the sales of Division 1 and 2,
and because of the new division that was just created
at this rate
Division 3 will be dissolved.
Division 3 is going to get dissolved after all, huh?
I'm worried about who is going to take over for Manten-sama.
You knew about this, right Chief Inuzuka?
Yeah.
I was going to tell everyone when the time comes.
Of course Division 3 is an important place for me.
No matter how many times I tried talking to the higher ups, I was not strong enough.
I'm sorry.
There is still hope.
There's this COOL JAPAN competition that Asai from Division 1 looked up.
It's a big project that will be held in Singapore next year.
If we get this project,
there might still be a chance that Division 3 will survive.
No good will come with doing something unnecessary like this.
If there something that I can do, then I want to do it.
That's unlike you, Nakano.
I don't want Division 3 to go away.
Me too.
I feel the same way.
It's impossible.
We should avoid taking risks.
He's right.
Are you fine if Division 3 goes away, Saruwatari-san?
Let's do it then.
Well said, Saru.
Thank you everyone.
Maybe Division 3 is on the verge of death, but
let's turn things around with this.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Division 3's Last Shooting.
What do you mean by that? It's scary though.
I messed up.
Don't worry about it.
Our feelings became one, right?
Yes.
It takes a variety of techniques to complete Last Shooting.
And there's no right answer when it comes to plastic models.
That's nonsense.
I will do it.
I head this from Shinji-san,
he said that you're really busy at work.
This is more like wishful thinking.
It's one of those moments that happen a few times in your life.
That's right.
Alright.
We're going to make the base kit.
Okay.
Open the box.
How to present the good points of Japan to Singapore?
In the past, major event companies has a stronghold on events of this magnitude.
The project is the key to stand out from the pack.
Not just introducing Japanese culture as is,
how about we combine the culture of Japan and Singapore and make a hybrid presentation.
Riko...
That's a good idea.
Asai suggested that to me.
I was taken aback because I thought that you came up with that.
What? What do you mean by that?
Alright, let's go with that.
Okay.
It's a legendary scene that any Gundam fan knows about.
A miracle that was produced by the Gundam without a head and left arm.
I can see the story looking by looking at the plastic model that you built.
Let's build your very own Last Shooting, Zakunee.
Okay.
Thanks.
This is a Master Grade.
Because you're going to build the insides too, the amount of parts is a lot more than an old kit and a High Grade.
It still looks cool if you can see the insides after making modifications, that is what Master Grade is all about.
Alright.
This one...
It's done.
Gundam.
There it is.
The temporary assembly is done.
Okay then, now decide the parts that you want to modify.
I leave the designs of the booths to you, Kijimura-san.
The stage and ideas, also leave that to me!
Yo! Kijimura!
I'm off.
The theme is Japanese culture, but
traditionally there are Kabuki, Noh, Japanese dance, Sumo and many more.
But recently there are a lot of famous Japanese contents such as manga, anime, games and vtubers.
Recently, Japanese foods such as dashi (soup stock) and umami (flavor) were also explored in depth.
Shinji.
Yes?
That was well researched.
Thank you very much.
Good job, Shinji.
Let's narrow it down.
Okay.
I will choose them.
I'm going to support you, so let's do this together.
I got the list of animation companies that we have ties to from Division 1.
Good job, Saru!
Did you get it from Oishi-san and Asai?
The fact that they're helping us out is top secret.
Okay, let's take it up a notch.
Okay.
You've been working all this time, you should take a rest, Zakunee.
I can still go on.
Don't overdo it.
Okay.
You're going to destroy the left arm.
I'm really nervous.
This is my first time seeing someone build Last Shooting.
Use the nipper and go wild.
It's even harder than doing it meticulously.
Here I go.
Huh?
I think that I can't do it.
Is it hard?
That's not it.
How do I put it?
That is the correct response.
You now love plastic models, Riko.
So your heart rejects the fact that you're going to destroy it yourself.
You don't have to do it.
This is my wishful thinking.
Please forgive me.
Alright.
Well done.
What's next?
That is all for today.
But, it's...
It's already late.
I'm sorry for staying here until this late.
Go home and sleep!
Okay.
Please check this, Nakano-san.
Chief, can I ask you to do the presentation?
Of course.
Should I use a pomade for the first time in a long time?
Because the animation company needs a little bit more of a push, I'm going to go see them in person.
I leave it to you.
I'm going too.
Let me help you.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Thanks.
So reliable.
I really want for Division 3 to survive.
There's no other division as kind as Division 3.
It's the most comfortable place in the world.
Let's fight to protect the most comfortable place in the world.
Okay.
It's nearly time to clock out.
What can we do now?
What about praying for the presentation to succeed and have fish and sake?
Let's pray.
Let's go.
We're going to start the painting process today.
Okay.
Next up is put on some ink.
Add shadows to create a three-dimensional effect.
Okay.
Next, use the gray ink.
Wait.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
Of course.
Next up is weathering the damaged parts.
Weathering.
Imagine just what kind of adventures that this thing has gone trough
the goal is to get close to what we have in mind as possible.
It is truly the ultimate imagination!
Finally, use the matting spray as the topcoat.
Okay.
I can see the what it's going to look like.
We can finally see the light at the end of the tunnel, right?
You won't get any strength if you only eat salad, Riko-san.
I don't have an appetite.
Did you get enough sleep, Riko?
I'm fine.
You've already talked to the general manager about this, right?
No, I'm just about to.
It's quite a large budget proposal, though.
No matter how you look at it, this wont pass the internal review.
My intention is to push this trough, even if it means my head is on the chopping block.
There's a chance that you might be fired and not get the green light, right?
How can you say that?
Are you alright?
Take a seat.
Sit down.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It seems like she's really busy with work.
Did you hear that from Shinji?
That's irrelevant.
You did well.
You're so cool.
It's about Division 3, right?
I can't do anything about it alone.
I know that.
I don't want you to completely turn the tables.
What is it?
That sounds fun.
Isn't it great that we got to dream for a while?
It was fun.
Agreed.
I feel sorry about not thinking about your position, Chief Inuzuka.
I have thought about it without sleep.
Even if I failed spectacularly,
I want to show everyone a cool side of me.
I'm going to show you what a man of the Showa era is made of.
Even if you fail spectacularly, It will only be traumatic for your subordinates.
Reiwa is not even going to let me go out spectacularly.
There's no need for someone to die.
I got the assurance from the President that we'll get the permission to participate in this competition.
He's my colleague after all.
You're so amazing, Acting Chief!
Kijimura-san, thank you very much.
To be honest, my resolve is up in the air, but...
Okay, let's all lift Kijimura up!
Let's get back to work, everyone.
Okay.
I see.
I leave it to you, Chief.
Do I look okay?
You look perfect.
Chief Inuzuka.
For you.
Gunpla?
This is a scene called Last Shooting.
That is the one that you said the other day?
That's right.
Now you can settle it once and for all.
I'm entrusting you with this, Chief.
That's perfect.
This doesn't have a head...
It's time.
Is the implication that I'm the only one who's going to get fired?
Okay.
I am honored to participate in the presentation of this very important event to introduce Japanese culture to the people of Singapore.
Not just Japanese culture like Kabuki, anime, vtubers, etc.,
we will also incorporate the culture of Singapore
and create an unprecedented event space.
And lastly,
I believe our company can create the best event possible.
Thank you very much.
I think only you could have done it, Inuzuka-kun.
Good work.
Do you want everyone to lift you up?
No, we won!
Thanks.
The things that I learned here, is my treasure.
Thank you for taking good care of me.
Thank you very much.
There are lots to do in HR.
Yes.
I'm going to show that I can become a Gundam here.
What are you talking about?
Do your best.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Is everyone ready?
Yes.
Let's share a toast.
Okay.
Yeah...
Well...
Anyway...
It was fun working with everyone in Division 3.
Cheers!
We got heated, that was so unlike us.
Even though we're going to be on different divisions,
let's do our very best.
I was surprised by just how much relaxed Division 3 is when I first joined.
It was a bit more on edge when I came here.
Everyone...
Even though everyone went along with my proposal...
It was all to protect the most comfortable place on earth.
I will fight for that sake.
Komukai.
Nobody forced us to participate.
Thank you very much.
Lately,
The gap between me and everyone has shrunk because of plastic models and work.
Woah.
"I made such a face".
I laughed.
In trouble.
Surprisingly serious.
I don't know when to give up.
I got to know a lot of different sides of me.
I...
More than I think...
Division 3...
My life...
I got attatched to them.
I can't sort out my feelings right now though...
Don't worry.
I'm over 40 and still can't understand my own feelings.
My...
My Last Shooting with everyone failed...
I'm so frustrated.
You fool.
Isn't it your First Shooting?
Komukai!
You can still see Oishi-san now.
Riko!
Go!
Go wild!
Youth is a right!
Even if you fail, don't regret it!
There is no data that says it's impossible.
Komukai...
Do it for me too!
Komukai RIko, is off!
Oishi-san!
Oishi-san.
I love you!
Will you go out with me?
Did you got rejected, Zakunee?
What should I build next?
Did he tell you that he only sees you as a little sister?
I've made my mind up.
What are you going to build?
Himeji castle and Gundam.
A collaboration.
That's good.
You can do anything with plastic models.
Okay.
Let's get to work...
I'm sleepy, so I'm going home.
Is that so?