masssterchief
Komukai.
Family day?
We're also going to participate, so I leave that to you.
What are we going to do?
We're going to invite the families of our colleagues and show them around the office.
So it's like a class visit then?
If anything, it's a cultural festival.
I couldn't forget how much fun the preparation on the day before the event,
that is the reason that I'm in this field.
Cultural festival.
Oishi-kun from Department 1 is heading up the whole project.
Oishi-san?
What should we do?
Should we make a Manten-kun t-shirts for Deparment 3?
Let's get hyped more than Department 1 and 2!
Okay.
I'm counting on you, Komukai!
Leave it to me!
Let's get started then.
Department 1 is in charge of the main event.
Department 2 is in charge of the food and beverages.
And Department 3 is in charge of the kids' space.
The families of our colleagues are our clients.
So don't let your guard down.
It looks like it's going to be a tough day.
Clients?
Let's create something that is enjoyable.
Is this work?
The main event is to conduct a tour of the company in the style of a real-life escape game.
This seems like something that me and my kids can enjoy together.
After completion, they will get a newspaper with the list of internal achievements of the participating employee.
Every employee is the star.
This matches with today's trends, this is great!
What do you think?
What about someone without any achievements?
There is no such person.
I see.
We can enjoy dishes from different countries for lunch.
An around the world buffet.
Be mindful about the amount of food and the budget.
Yes.
Thank you.
So, tell me about the Department 3's proposal for the kids' space.
Ring toss.
Ring toss?!
Did you brought a proposal?
It's only a ring toss.
I'm going to think about it one more time.
Okay.
What are we going to do for family day?
I haven't decided just yet.
What? It's this weekend, right?
I couldn't come up with a project that will be green lit by Oishi-san.
He's always working 24/7, right?
The power of the Ace is scary.
Let us do what we want, it's not work after all.
What are you doing over there Shinji?
What is that?
It's Gunplas!
Kijimura-san!
Z'GOK!
Is that a stack of plastic models?
What do you mean by that?
DOM!
Jet stream attack!
Are you going to open a plastic model shop or something?
That's a good idea.
At the shop that Riko-san introduced me to, I ended up buying it because of Chiemi-san's passion.
I feel like the increasing amount of boxes is the representation of our intimacy.
What an easy customer, you are.
What?
I didn't do such a thing.
Avante!
Emperor!
What?
Avante!
Is that a Dragon Quest spell?
No!
It's a mini 4WD!
I didn't know that there's a RS model of Avante.
Is there a Thunder Shot?
Fire Dragon.
Shining Scorpion.
Mammoth Dump Truck.
Wildsaurus.
Lunch Box Jr.
Put yourself in the shoes of the one being named!
This is cool, don't you think so?
That's right, it's the Emperor!
The name "Emperor" is so cool.
Nobody can go against it.
Don't say weird things.
Do they move?
Of course!
I'm going to say it one more time,
it's a mini 4WD!
Mini 4WD?
President.
Good work.
What's with the mini 4WD?
Well...
You look like you're having the time of your life.
That's right, we are preparing for the family day.
The young ones wanted to play with mini 4WD, isn't that right Komukai?
That's right.
Department 3 is going with mini 4WD.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
You heard him, so I'm counting on you, Komukai.
Okay.
Mini 4WD race, FUNFUN Cup.
Komukai.
We're part ot the Events Department.
What's with this proposal?
There are better options than this, like VR attractions.
I can lend you the gear that we used before for an event.
Really?
Yeah.
Is it okay with you, Oishi-san?
Well.
Mini 4WD is okay.
What?
Mini 4WD is just...
This is something that Komukai-san came up with.
No, I was just...
Asai!
Department 3 is in charge of this.
Proceed with this.
Okay.
Oishi-san gave his approval.
Is that so?
Alright Komukai, we're going all out.
All out?
That's right.
We're going to build a huge circuit,
and invite Mini 4WD Fighter to commentate on the races!
It's going to be so exciting!
Mini 4WD Fighter?
-That's right.
Is he your friend?
Of course he's not my friend, he's a legend.
You don't know him?
No, I don't.
Riko, does Shinji really like plastic models?
Of course, he always bought something when he's here.
I won't approve of him.
It looks like Shinji-kun likes to stack plastic model boxes.
We don't sell plastic models for that purpose.
Yassan, you are wavering too much between your business and your beliefs.
I'm sure that the plastic models are sad because it's untouched.
Of course I want him to build them, but he's our rare regular customer.
Why are you defending him?
His goal is...
What are you looking for today, Zakunee?
Mini 4WD was first released in 1982.
With a price that was affordable to elementary school kids,
you became an owner once you bought one,
you became a mechanic once you made modifications,
and you can become a racer once you took it out.
It's the world's first motorsport.
Children can feel the infinite possibilities of the future or the world in the palm of their hands.
Everyone wants to be a pro.
This year marks the 40th anniversary of the Mini 4WD.
There are more than 400 types of cars that went on sale,
the total lifetime sales sits at more than 180 million units.
It created a social phenomenon in the past.
You can't control it,
But, that's okay.
Once it's up and running, you just watch over it.
Just watching over it?
Mini 4WD takes adults back to their youth,
kids go crazy over it.
In other words, adults go crazy over it.
What?
It means that everyone can enjoy it.
Go to a whole new world, Riko!
Komukai...
-Wait a second, Riko-san.
Please invite me if you're going to the plastic model shop!
I'll take this.
Shinji-kun, Yajima Model Shop is having second thoughts about you.
Second thoughts?
It seems like Chiemi-chan actually wants you to build those plastic models.
Understood.
You're quick to understand.
So please invite me next time you're going there.
Okay.
You're quick to understand.
You're doing it.
You're just getting started?
That's right.
I'm going to lend a hand.
Let's get this all out.
You just push it in.
It's done.
Looking good.
Alright, I'm going to get you up and running in no time.
Alright.
This is nerve racking.
There it is.
Alright, what do you think?
Let's go!
What do you think about my youth?
It was nerve racking thinking about whether it will return to me or not.
This sure makes me happy.
The sound is amazing, right?
Woah, that's something else.
Hey, it makes you get a nosebleed, right?
Not at all.
What's wrong?
What?
I want to hear what Komukai-san has to say about the newspaper sample...
It's Victory Magnum!
Did you used to play with this too, Oishi-kun?
No...
You used to play with Mini 4WD, didn't you?
Yes...
I knew it.
You liked it, huh...
When I read Komukai-san's proposal,
I was so excited that I almost let out a scream.
You should have told us earlier.
So, how about tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
-Yes.
We're going to race after we finished building our cars.
It's precisely because it's on the day before the event.
Rehearsal is an important part of the job, right?
Yes, you're right.
Alright, let's get hyped for the FUNFUN Cup eve.
Eve.
Let's modify our cars.
Modify?
Yes.
Modification is the best part of mini 4WD.
It seems like modification is an obsession.
In other words, it's eden.
The one that is the best at cornering, wins the race.
It's not that simple, Shinji.
Speed or cornering, it all depends on the course.
What kind of modifications are you going to make, Komukai-san?
Nothing.
No no no...
You have to make modifications, or you're not going to win.
I'm fine with not winning.
But why?
I'm happy if it came back to me in one piece.
So, I'm not going to do anything to it.
Oh...
I see...
Komukai-san.
Oishi-san?
Hey...
Let's make modifications after all.
What?
You came all the way just to say that?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Last confirmation.
I've read this.
Thank you for compiling things that sounds like my achievements.
You're wrong,
that is your actual achievements.
I see.
Oishi-san.
Yes?
Is making modifications dangerous?
No, not at all.
What?
Let's do it.
Okay.
Sorry for being late.
Good morning...
Woah.
Good morning.
What are those?
I've gathered all the necessary parts.
Let's get started.
Okay.
The cars hit this section right here.
You're not going to start making modifications??
We have to know the characteristics of the course before making modifications.
You're taking that off too?
Yes.
For super fast gear,
we use Hyper-Dash Motor.
Come again?
It's like soy sauce on top of rice with egg.
You can't go without it.
That's right.
Next up.
We going to change the normal tires to large diameter narrow lightweight tires.
Large diameter narrow...
Okay.
So thin.
Make sure the rollers are straight.
It's straight.
Okay.
Go straight.
Thank you.
Can it move?
It's good.
It's finally time for the meat removal.
Meat removal?
First of all, we're going to take off the stickers.
Eh? Why?
Because it's called meat removal.
Don't worry.
I have another one with me.
It's time.
Gently.
Meat removal, complete!
Yes!
Have you always liked it?
That...
Victory Magnum?
That's right.
It's more like I long for it.
You long for it?
Yeah.
It's because back in elementary school, this one was everyone's hero.
It's a machine that screams protagonist.
I see that it was really popular back then.
I really wanted one, but,
after I saw this at the store
I began having second thoughts.
I didn't buy it in the end.
I thought that you always have the life of a protagonist.
Why do you think so?
You're way off the mark.
Alright.
If we're done building it, we have to say "Give birth!"
What?
Ready...
Victory Magnum, give birth!
Did I say it right?
Yes.
Speed is everything, even light is jealous.
Lightning Avante Jr.
The emperor of love that rules over all corners,
Emperor Chiemi.
The protagonist that is late to the party,
Big Stone Victory Magnum.
Big Stone?
[His name literally means Big Stone]
Are you ready?
Ready?
Go!
Go go go!
It sure can jump high.
Inuzuka-san's Avante is too dangerous.
A master at going off course.
Your Emperor is too slow!
I put too much emphasis on cornering.
Magnum is running smoothly.
Komukai-san, just by having it come back in one piece makes me happy after all.
I want to show this to you back in elementary school.
I used a pomade for the first time in 2nd grade and made my pompadour debut.
I used to go to cram school 6 days a week, so I don't have any recollection of playing around.
The snacks for our field trip was Apolo chocolate and Hi-Chew.
That doesn't change much between our generations.
I modified the handle of my bike to look like a Harley-Davidson handle.
Every week I would swap the rankings of my favorite girls and write them down in my notebook.
That is so scary.
That ain't good.
I'm proud of this fact, I was the one who wore Levi's first on our class.
I was aiming for all 3's for my report card, so I purposely ran slowly.
The whole class found out that I had a crush on the teacher,
it was hell on earth.
Did the teacher called you over?
Yes.
That's amazing.
I'm sure that you were popular back in the day, Oishi-kun.
Not at all.
I wasn't in the position to invite people to go play together.
I was always waiting for someone to invite me.
That is so surprising to hear.
I mean, when we had to split into groups of two,
my heart was beating so fast because I was so nervous.
In my case, I called them out all at once.
How does that work actually?
Is it like when you're out with 4 other friends, but you can't seem to join their conversation?
That's right.
Before you know it, they're talking among themselves and you're all alone.
It's not like you're being excluded or anything, right?
And you can't give a good response when they actually speak to you.
Pretending to listen to their conversation, but in reality you space out.
I totally get it.
Huh?
The two of you sounds like two peas in a pod.
Is that so?
Yeah.
I feel like the two of you are going to be best buddies if you're in the same class.
Not at all.
I think that probably neither of us will call each other out.
Even if we talk to each other, it's not going to be interesting at all.
Hey!
Do you want to play at the rooftop tomorrow?
Are you ready everyone?
Ready? Go!
Komukai-san.
Everyone is excited.
Yes.
Do you like that band?
What?
Yeah.
That's great.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Are the two of you a couple?
What?
Do we look like a couple?
Yes.