masssterchief
Thank you for everything
Do your best!
Please leave it to me!
Excuse me
As of today, I've been reassigned to Events Department 3
It's my 2nd year working here, my name is Takagi Shinji
Nice to meet everyone
It's unusual to be reassigned at this time of year
A rookie...
2nd year...
Weren't you in department 1?
That's right, I came from Events Department 1
Getting reassigned from department 1 to 3...
What did you do?
What did I do?
Is it "Se" or "Po"?
Are you talking about Pro Baseball League?
Sexual harassment or Power harassment
Or is it "Re"?
Remote harassment?!
My first ever junior
Excuse me, can I have your attention?
Go ahead
I found four areas for improvement in this department just by taking a quick glance
What?
The first one is
it's inefficient to manually put all of these flyers into an envelope
It's better to just outsource this and use your time to get more projects instead
It's a more effective use of your time
This is to show our sincerity towards Manten Nodoame-san
That is the second improvement point
80% of this department's sales is from Manten Nodoame
Don't you think that it's dangerous to just rely on one big client?
He's so unpleasant
The third point...
Well well
Let's take it easy
Okay then everyone
Let's do our best as a team
I don't think that I can deal with him
Because he's my junior, I can ask him to make copies of documents, right?
Listen up everyone
What?
What's with this atmosphere?
Thank you for your hard work
I've been reassigned from Department 1, my name is Takagi Shinji
Takagi Shinji-kun
Shinji it is
Meet you-nice to, Shinji
I've found the fifth area for improvement
Improvement?
Don't you have something to say, Inuzuka-kun?
That's right Kijimura-san
Listen up everyone
Department 3 is now in charge of a sports car PR event
What?
Don't you think that the project is too big? Are you kidding me?
Department 1 can't handle it, so it was passed down to us
There it is, the customary hand-me-down work for Department 3
When is the presentation?
In 3 days
What?
That's over the speed limit for Department 3
Everyone, would you like to go full throttle with me?
Excuse me
Making copies of the presentation documents should be done by my junior Shinji-kun, right?
Yeah
That's still a long ways off, Komukai
Sports car is a fashion item for men
Okay
Having a cute girl on the passenger seat
and then cutting trough the wind in Shonan beach
Men will shine when riding a sports car
Don't you think so, Kijimura-san?
That's right
But don't you think that it's a bit old fashioned?
A sports car should be like going through a pass at high speed and then drifts
That sounds cool
People call me the explosive kid from Nerima
You're a racer, Saruwatari?
Intial D
You're talking about an arcade in Nerima then
Excuse me
I think that we should proceed based on facts, not by vague impressions
Facts?
What is the target demographic for the event?
I think that it's working people in their 40's and under
I see
In other words, it's me and Nakano-san
What is it?
The point is how to bring sports car closer to young people
That's right, that is what we want
Or how to bring young people closer to sports car
What?
I think that it's better for just us, young people, to work on this presentation
Please take a look at this data
More than 50% of people in their 20's said that they don't need a car
The number is even higher when it comes to sports car
The reason is that they don't want to stand out,
they don't know when to drive it,
it's not a status symbol as it used to be, and so on
We can sympathize with these kind of answers
But, just the three of you...
The truth is that I used to ride my Grandfather's Porsche
Your grandfather's Porsche...
The luxurious glossy seats and sunsets by the sea
I was deeply moved as a child back then
Your grandfather's Porsche...
What a wonderful memory, just like a gem
Don't you think that it's better to leave it to these young people over here, Kijimura-san?
Agreed
Go for it, Shinji
Of course
Go for it, all of you
Wait just a sec
Excuse me
What did he meant by "Go for it"?
Hey you, are you dumb or are you smart?
It's the key to changing the perception of sports car
To that end, the ones who think about how to achieve it must be young as well
He seems smart
Young people these days are very rational
So we can win if we can show that value of owning a sports car outweighs the price and inconvenience
Yup
It sounds like we're making progress, but we're actually not
Okay then, the two of you, let's come up with a plan in this direction
Can we meet up again tomorrow?
Of course! What about you, Riko?
I'll do my best until it's time to go home
No need to worry
I'm here
Let's talk about this again tomorrow
I'm immediately tired because of him
Don't you think that the capable vibes that he gives off in his 2nd year is amazing?
Hear me out, sports car is a dream of every man
Excuse me, another round on the rocks please
I don't care about all of that, but
What car did you drive back then?
Nissan Silvia
I was shining back then, but
now I drive a car with sliding doors
Sliding doors, huh?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about before I know it, I'm riding a family car with sliding doors
I totally get it
Aren't you single, Saruwatari-san?
Is the project going to be okay, Nakano?
Yes, Shinji said that there's no need to worry
That's not reassuring at all
I guess that you guys will hold back if we're part of the team
Do what you want young'uns
Say what's on your minds and get the project over the line
You're just scared of his grandfather's Porsche, aren't you?
Tell you the truth, I was shaking after I heard him say that
Welcome
Let's get started
Let's finish making the presentation today
Okay
Eh?
Yes?
No no no
What?
Yes?
Don't say that
I thought that you were going to come up with a plan
I said that let's come up with a plan in direction to the two of you
Why did you say "No need to worry" and "I'm here" then
That's why I'm here right now
You meant that literally?
Is there any other meaning?
This person is crazy after all
Nakano-san
Even if you're angry, nothing will come of it
Calm down
Riko, it's better if we do this just the two of us
What?
Shinji
Yes
You can go home now
But...
I got some sharp insights from you, so it's all good, right Riko?
Yes, it's all good
If everything is alright, then I'm going to leave it to the two of you
Listen up, presentation is a battle of passion
The rareness of a sports car...
Stop talking
Okay then, please excuse me
Having a presentation in 2 days is really tough
A battle of passion
What's wrong?
Is presentation all about our passion, Nakano-san?
That has got nothing to do with it
As long as we succeed, it doesn't matter
How much is a sports car anyway?
No
20 million
20 million?!
Who buys a sports car then?
Either a rich person or a dreamer
Why do people call it sports car?
Cars that was developed with an emphasis on the enjoyment of sports driving
The explosive kid from Nerima
That was an indoor arcade kid
Oh yeah
You're amazing
Tell us, Google
Projection mapping
This is it
Yeah
I missed the regular time to go home
From now on, we're going to waste our time the most in our lives
What about this?
Looks good
That's more like it
Okay, let's go with this
Leave the presentation to me
You're the top runner in the not-passionate world, Nakano-san
Who cares about passion?
Okay, I'm going to buy some drinks
Okay then, let's go home by 18:30
Huh?
You're still here, Komukai-san?
Ooishi-san
Good work
I'm going to go home by 18:30
I see
Is that the sports car project?
That's right
So you're the one in charge of the project
Can I take a look?
Thank you
What do you think?
How do I say it...
There is nothing that appeals to me
Something that appeals to you...
I wonder...
Maybe it's the distance between you and the car
Have you fallen for sports car?
What?
Don't you think that being in charge of the promotion means that conveying the charms of said product?
But you can only see the charms after you've fallen for it
I see
You still have a lot of time
as something that you came up with in a hurry, it's fine
Thank you very much
Good work
I didn't came up with this in a hurry though...
What's wrong?
Do you love sports car, Nakano-san?
Of course not
As expected...
But, it looks like that we have to love it or else...
Or else? Why is that?
What?
Can I go home now?
Is everthing okay?
I'm going to see if I can properly love it or not
Good evening
What?
Could it be...
You want more?
More?
Isn't it Zaku-Oneesan
Are you looking for another plastic model?
Is it really unusual?
Having someone come for more is a miracle
Is unthinkable for a young women customer to come here again for the second time
What brings you here today?
I want to look for something
Zaku-nee
Yes?
That is the beginning of your plastic model journey
Plastic model journey?
Welcome to our side
Found it
Don't overdo it
Are you okay, Zaku-nee?
I'm sorry
This looks like it
Nissan R35 GT-R
It's a 2014 model GT-R by Nissan
A gran turismo with a high quality and comfortable riding experience and the overwhelming speed of it's racing technology
With those two qualities, it's a dream car for adults who are after those two qualities
It's a high end Japanese made sports car for those who continue to yearn for the glorious days of their youth
The price...
That's right
Around 10 million
But,
It's 3,740 yen for the plastic model
I'll buy it then
By the way, the body is centered on it's back side
Okay then, Riko-san
It's okay to buy it and then go home
or it's also okay to build it here
"Open the box"
Don't forget to put your seat belt on
What?
Riko-san, please go full throttle!
Okay
Okay then
Riko is off
Open the box
What?
What's wrong?
It's completely different from the Zaku
The parts are too detailed
It's packed with dreams
It's actually a nightmare
Giving up already, Zaku-nee?
Sports cars are getting further and further away
Don't worry,
plastic models also teaches you how to overcome difficulties
Huh?
Is this it?
That is for the tires
By placing a spring over there, it can realistically simulate the bouncy feeling of a real car
The same as a real car
Carefully cutting the parts out of the runner
You will damage the parts itself if you're too aggressive
Leave a bit of the gates on the parts, because you're going to smooth it out later
This too, huh?
It's so small
You missed one
That is the radiator hose, an important part of the car
That was close
So small
Are you going to assemble it already?
What?
Because it's a sports car, I'm sure want to paint it to look cool
Yes, but it's completely different from the Zaku
Just this once...
What?
So cool
It looks real, doesn't it?
Just this once
Okay
Wow, it's so detailed
It's where people sit on the car
Put it on while thinking about who's going to sit on it
Who is on your mind?
I wanted to ride it alone
Well, imagine it's you then
I don't have a driver's license
Just put it on
Eh?
I can't do it, it's too small
You can do it, Zaku-nee
That part is the equivalent to a human's heart
The car won't move without it
What? This plastic model can move?
No
Why should I put it on then?
It's because it's the heart
Alright
So precious
Why did you paint it red?
Because it's the heart
The engine looks better in silver
That's fine
You can do anything with plastic models
Alright
Huh?
What's wrong?
Once I put the body on, the engine is no longer visible
That's right
It's not visible, even though it was hard to assemble it
We put our heart and soul into it, even into the invisible internal parts
That is the great thing about this scale model
The plastic model journey, I still have a long way to go
It snapped on
GT-R, give birth!
Well done
This feels so heavy for some reason
Because it's filled with dreams
You loved sports car, don't you Zaku-nee?
Not at all
I was just looking for a reason to love it
When you're looking for a reason, your love for it is already up and running
I already love it...
This time, we would like to propose the Five Senses Showroom
It's a PR event where people can actually experience interacting with parts of a dissembled sports car
If you count all the parts of a car down to the smallest screws, there are more than 30.000 parts in total
Our goal is to bring young people and sports car closer by letting them interact with parts of the car that people don't really get to see
I see
By the way, how did you come up with the idea for this project?
Riko
Yes
I build a plastic model of a sports car after I was entrusted with this project
Plastic model?
That's right
Forgive me for saying this, but at first I don't understand why would someone buy a sports cars
That's why I build it as something to get me to love it
And then,
every single parts looked so cool
I became gradually drawn into it
The beautiful internal parts, that is hard to imagine from the outside, is packed with a lot of parts and technologies
I thought that it's so precious
If a 1/24th scale of a car can make me this excited,
a real car would be even more exciting
That is all for our presentation
Thank you very much
Everyone
About the sports car event...
The client accepted it
What?
Good job
Thank you very much
Good work
Great job! Did you bribe them or something?
Of course not
Good work Nakano-san, Riko-san
I read your proposal
You really took the concepts that I said to heart
It's all thanks to you, Shinji
Nothing less from the former Department 1 member
Thank you very much
But there are 5 areas that need improvement
Improvement?
First of all is the we didn't prepare a backup plan
Normally we would prepare plan A, B and C...
I should give him a proper beat down
Don't you agree, Riko?